Guide to the Women's Center records, 1970-2005, bulk 1983-2005 UA.09.17.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA2006-0047, 1984-2002, 4 boxes
  - Annual Report to the Faculty, 1997 [President Keohane's State of the University Address] (Box 13)
  - Women's Coalition Notes, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Women's Coalition - Correspondence/Memo, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Women's Coalition Financials, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Women's Coalition Materials, 1995 (Box 13)
- UA2008-0071, 1986-2005, 1 boxes
  Accession subject files, memoranda, annual reports, correspondence, and other materials with inclusive dates 1986-2005. Major subjects include Sexual Assault Support Services (SASS), Take Back the Night, and Duke Women's Handbooks.
  - Annual Reports (Programming and Women's Center), 1993-1997 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports (Programming and Women's Center), 1997-1999 (Box 14)
  - Cappuccino and Jazz Program, 1992 (Box 14)
  - Career Exploration Luncheon for Undergraduate Women, 1991 (Box 14)
  - EarthHeart (Saphira Linden) - Spirituality, 1998 (Box 14)
  - GPWN Schedules of Events, Summer 2000-Spring 2002 (Box 14)
  - Lesbian/Bisexual Programming, 1993 (Box 14)
  - Lisa Kellmeyer/Seulky Shin Administrative Response [re: medical services treatment services available at Duke for rape survivors] (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 [contains brochures, flyers, memos] (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous, Women's Coalition, 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Rape Awareness Week, 1994; 1997-2000 (Box 14)
  - Rape and Sexual Assault Task Force, 1991-1993
    - Response Protocol for Sexual Assault of Duke Students, 1992 and Report to the Security Task Force, 1993 (Box 14)
  - Sexual Assault Support Services (SASS), 1989-1991 [articles, ads, clippings, etc] (Box 14)
  - SASS Activity Reports, 1992-1997 (Box 14)
  - SASS Brochures and Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 14)
  - SASS Introduction Letter, 1991 (Box 14)
  - Sexual Assault Prevention Week, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Sexual Assault Brochures, 1992 (Box 14)
  - Sexual Harassment Graduate Women Incidence Survey, 1991 (Box 14)
  - Take Back the Night, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Take Back the Night, 1991 (Box 14)
  - Take Back the Night, 1992 (Box 14)
  - Take Back the Night Articles, 1993 (Box 14)
  - Duke Women's Handbook, 1988-1989; 1991-1994, 1995-2002, 11 handbooks (Box 14)
  - Women's Center Budget, FY1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Women's Center Goals and Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 14)
  - Women's Center Programming, 1993-1995, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - WISE Programming, Fall 1996; 1999-2001 (Box 14)
  - Women's Center Task Force Advisory Board, 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - Women's Coalition, 2001-2002 (Box 14)